NEWSLETTERS

Emailed Daily. Always Free!

* 
* MY FAVORITES
* SPORTS
* RESOURCES

* ···

    ### Follow Us

* NEWSLETTERS  
    Emailed Daily. Always Free!

Privacy Policy
==============

YB Media, LLC  
Last updated: October 5, 2018

Thank you for your interest in YB Media, LLC, ("YB Media") and our website located at https://www.yardbarker.com (the "Service"). Your use of the Service is subject to this Privacy Policy. We are pleased to provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our practices with respect to how we collect and use personally identifiable information in connection with your use of the Service.

This Privacy Policy covers:

What Information Do We Collect?

When you use the Service, the information that we collect falls into two categories: 1) Personal Information, which includes information that you provide when you register an account or sign up for a newsletter, and 2) Non-Personal Information collected through technology

Personal Information

When you register for the Service, we may collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, email address, country and postal code. After you become a registered user, you may provide additional information in your profile section. Providing additional information is optional.

Non-Personal Information

We employ various Internet technologies to automatically collect certain types of non-personal information when you access or use the Service.

Cookies, Pixel Tags, Local Storage and Similar Technologies. In order to collect this data, we may utilize automated tools and files such as "cookies", "pixel tags" and Local Storage Objects. These automated tools and files may reside on our servers or on your computer or device. These technologies allow us to manage access to the Service, provide you with customization of the Service, and understand how our audience uses the Service. If you restrict our ability to use these automated tools and files, your ability to access and use all or part of the Service may be limited or disabled completely.

Device Information. The Service is provided through your computer, tablet, mobile device, or other internet connected device. You agree that we may collect and use non-personal technical data and related information about your device, including but not limited to: unique device identifiers, the IP address of your device, geolocation information, the manufacturer and model of your device, your operating system and browser type, browser language and other transactional information.

How Do We Use This Information?

To Operate the Service. We use your personally identifiable information primarily to provide you with the Service, to facilitate communication between users, to provide customized content on the Service that is of interest to you, to provide relevant advertising on the Service and to improve the Service. The information is also used to verify your authority to access the Service and to contact you when reasonably necessary.

Personalization. In order to provide you with content and advertising that is more interesting and relevant to you, we may use the information from and about you to make inferences and predictions about your potential areas of interest. We may also use aggregate and anonymous data about your use of and activity on the YB Media services to assist us in this regard.

Interactive Features. From time to time, we may offer interactive features including, but not limited to: quizzes, polls, comment threads, contests, games, message boards, forums, user-to-user messaging, etc. Some of these features may require the use of your personal information in order to operate the feature. The use of these features is voluntary.

Customer Support and Notifications. We may also use any information you have provided as reasonably necessary to administer or provide customer support for the Service, and to provide you with periodic e-mail communications, including newsletters and notifications about new products and services, special promotions or upcoming events. Users may choose not to receive such newsletters and notifications.

Email Newsletters. We operate several email newsletters. If you no longer wish to receive a specific newsletter, click the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email, and follow the appropriate instructions. If you have any difficulty with the Unsubscribe functionality, please contact [unsubscribe@yardbarker.com](mailto:unsubscribe@yardbarker.com).

Statistical Analysis. We also use such information for research and analytical purposes, for product development purposes, to measure the performance of the Service, to generally understand how the Service is used, so as to improve the Service.

With Whom Do We Share This information?

Third Parties. We use a select number of trusted external service providers who help us provide and maintain the Service (including, but not limited to: analytics companies, advertisers and ad agencies, data management and storage services, survey providers). These service providers are carefully selected for their high standards in regard to data protection and privacy. In those circumstances, YB Media may disclose your personal information, in our sole discretion, so that such service providers may perform those services. These service providers are only permitted to use your information to the extent necessary to enable them to provide their services to us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your personally identifiable information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question.

In addition, these third parties may place or recognize cookies or use other technology to track certain information about our users. For example, in the course of serving certain advertisements, an advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser in order to collect certain information about your use of the Service.

In particular, the Service uses certain Google analytics and other services, and certain pages use the Google AMP Client ID API, each of which may enable collection and sharing of your information (including personal data) with Google for further use. For specific information on Google usage and how to control it, please see [How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) and [Google's Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

In addition, YB Media may share your information with reputable business partners to permit them to send you marketing communications if this is consistent with your choices.

As Required By Law. In addition to the foregoing, we will disclose your personally identifiable information as it believes is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority or to prevent harm to yourself or others.

Upon a Sale, Merger or Bankruptcy. Finally, we may disclose your personally identifiable information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of YB Media's stock or assets in YB Media's line of business to which this Privacy Policy relates or upon any bankruptcy or other corporate reorganization.

How Can You Manage Your Information?

Profile Information. You can edit your personal information and email notification preferences by visiting your profile page at [https://www.yardbarker.com/user\_settings/profile](https://www.yardbarker.com/user_settings/profile).

Interactive Features. We may make available to users chat rooms, forums, comment threads, message boards, and other interactive features. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) via forums, postings, profiles or other areas of the Service, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of YB Media. Please do not post any personal information on the Service or in other areas that you expect to keep private. You may modify personal information that you have submitted using the Service by accessing the Service and updating your profile information.

Opting Out. If you wish for us remove all of your personal information, please contact [privacy@yardbarker.com](mailto:privacy@yardbarker.com).

How Long Do We Keep Your Information?

We still store your information as long as necessary for the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, unless you specifically edit it, or opt out (as described above). We may also retain information required by law.

Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies for interest-based advertising, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

To opt out, please visit [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/)

Third-Party Links and Referrals

For your convenience, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties' products or services. If you choose to visit a third party's website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party's privacy policy, and not the YB Media privacy policy, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with the third party.

Security Practices

Because any personally identifiable information you submit to YB Media is purely voluntary and should not be of a particularly sensitive nature, we employ standard security measures with respect to this information and do not use special encryption methods at this time. User accounts are secured by user-created passwords.

Please note that no method of data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. As such, we cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

It is your responsibility to take appropriate steps to protect against unauthorized access to your computer or mobile device. We are not responsible for any lost or stolen computers, phones, or other devices, or for any activity on your account via unauthorized access.

Children's Guidelines

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information relating to children. In the event that we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age without prior parental consent, we will take steps to promptly delete such information. By providing your personal information to us or through the Service, you represent that you are 13 years of age or older.

Policy Changes

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, and will post any revisions on the Service. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Service will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.

International Visitors and Users

The Service is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting from the European Union (EU) or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personal data you consent to:

1. The use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
2. The transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

No Error-Free Performance

We do not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve this Privacy Policy. You can provide feedback at [privacy@yardbarker.com](mailto:privacy@yardbarker.com). We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it.

Legal Notices

This Privacy Policy is subject to the terms in our Terms of Service, available for review at [https://www.yardbarker.com/terms](https://www.yardbarker.com/terms), including terms regarding limitations on damages, disclaimers of warranties, and resolution of disputes. Our Terms of Service take precedence over any conflicting provision in this Privacy Policy.

Questions

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at:

YB Media, LLC  
1534 Plaza Lane, #146  
Burlingame, CA 94010

FREE NEWSLETTERS

Copyright 2024 YB Media, LLC. All rights reserved.  
  
Use of this website (including any and all parts and  
components) constitutes your acceptance of these  
[Terms of Service](https://www.yardbarker.com/terms) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.yardbarker.com/privacy).  
  
This site is for entertainment purposes only.  
There is no gambling offered on this site.  
Gambling Problem? [Call 1-800-Gambler](https://www.ncpgambling.org/).
